There's a big event this month, right?
هناك حدث كبير هذا الشهر، أليس كذلك؟
I heard that on the day when the moon is the roundest all year,
سمعت أنه في اليوم الذي يكون فيه القمر أكثر استدارة طوال العام،
there will be an eclipse.
سيكون هناك كسوف.
If you miss this chance, you'll only be able to see it again 1,200 years from now.
إذا ضيعت هذه الفرصة، فلن تتمكن من رؤيتها مرة أخرى إلا بعد 1200 عام من الآن.
[Gildal]
[جيلدال]
Don't miss it.
لا تفوتها.
On such a special day,
في مثل هذا اليوم المميز،
what would it be like to pluck up your courage and be honest about your feelings for someone?
كيف سيكون الأمر لو جمعت شجاعتك وقلت بصراحة مشاعرك تجاه شخص ما؟
[The Story of Bihyung]
[قصة بيهيونغ]
[Hwang Jaewook]
[هوانغ جايووك]
[Lee Chamin]
[لي شامين]
[Kang Chanwoo]
[كانغ تشان وو]
[Nam Taekjun]
[نام تايكجون]
[Seo Heesun]
[هذا هو هيسون]
[The Story of Bihyung]
[قصة بيهيونغ]
But...
لكن...
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
No, I'm not moving. I have something to say.
لا، لن أتحرك. لدي شيء لأقوله.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Do you...
هل أنت...
like...
يحب...
What?
ماذا؟
I heard you used to like Dr. Jigwi a lot.
سمعت أنك كنت تحب الدكتور جيغوي كثيرًا.
Do you still like him?
هل لازلت تحبه؟
What?
ماذا؟
Jigwi?
هل هذا يساعد؟
Me?
أنا؟
Physical attachment.
الارتباط الجسدي.
I heard that it was a fierce one.
سمعت أنها كانت شرسة.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
أنت تعرف ما أتحدث عنه، أليس كذلك؟
What?
ماذا؟
Physical attachment?
الارتباط الجسدي؟
Not physical attachment, but a physical fight?
ليس ارتباطًا جسديًا، بل قتال جسدي؟
Not lovers, but enemies?
ليسوا عشاق بل أعداء؟
You're so young, but you know quite a bit.
أنت صغير جدًا، لكنك تعرف الكثير.
What?
ماذا؟
Physical attachment?
الارتباط الجسدي؟
Are those the fantasies you have of me all day long?
هل هذه هي التخيلات التي تراودك عني طوال اليوم؟
Not all day long.
ليس طوال اليوم.
Not all day long,
ليس طوال اليوم،
but you've thought about it.
لكنك فكرت في ذلك.
N-No, it's not like that.
ن-لا، ليس الأمر كذلك.
You were on the sofa with Dr. Jigwi this morning, right?
لقد كنت على الأريكة مع الدكتور جيجوي هذا الصباح، أليس كذلك؟
Hey.
يا.
Shall I show you what real physical attachment is like?
هل أريك كيف يكون الارتباط الجسدي الحقيقي؟
Article 4, Article 4!
المادة 4، المادة 4!
Hey, Ha Keumbok. Where are you going?
أهلاً، ها كومبوك. إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Let's build an attachment, too!
دعونا نبني مرفقًا أيضًا!
A physical one!
واحدة جسدية!
Huh?
هاه؟
Gildal.
جيلدال.
You finished your exercise so early today?
هل أنهيت تمرينك مبكرًا اليوم؟
I'm the only normal person in this house.
أنا الشخص الطبيعي الوحيد في هذا المنزل.
My wallet doesn't have a hole in it.
محفظتي لا يوجد بها ثقب.
How am I spending money just by breathing?
كيف أنفق أموالي بمجرد التنفس؟
When one leaves home, they're bound to suffer.
عندما يغادر الشخص منزله، فمن المؤكد أنه سيعاني.
Don't they say one should go out and suffer while they're young?
ألا يقولون أنه ينبغي على الإنسان أن يخرج ويعاني وهو شاب؟
10,000 won.
10,000 وون.
1,000 won, 1,000 won,
1000 وون، 1000 وون،
1,000 won.
1000 وون.
With this little money, it's even difficult to suffer,
مع هذا القليل من المال، من الصعب حتى المعاناة،
Mr. Ha Keumpoop.
السيد ها كومبوب.
Just because imagination is free, your gaze is flying everywhere...
لأن الخيال حر، نظرك يطير في كل مكان...
What?
ماذا؟
This is why they say humans are unpredictable and can't be trusted.
لهذا السبب يقولون أن البشر غير متوقعين ولا يمكن الوثوق بهم.
Why do you keep making fun of me?
لماذا تستمر بالسخرية مني؟
Hey, we're still charging.
مهلا، نحن لا نزال نشحن.
When will this charging ever be complete?
متى سيتم الانتهاء من هذه الشحنة؟
Except for when I'm working or sleeping, you've been holding my hand all day long.
باستثناء عندما أعمل أو أنام، كنت تمسك بيدي طوال اليوم.
If you keep doing this, my hands will get a rash.
إذا واصلت القيام بذلك، سوف تصاب يداي بالطفح الجلدي.
That's because you didn't want to get essence through the Gate of Hell!
هذا لأنك لم ترغب في الحصول على الجوهر من خلال بوابة الجحيم!
As for this,
أما بالنسبة لهذا،
how can you let someone's lips touch that?
كيف يمكنك السماح لشفتي شخص ما بلمس ذلك؟
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
I said it's the same as eating with your mouth.
قلت أنه مثل الأكل بالفم.
It's because we have to eat.
لأنه يتعين علينا أن نأكل.
I have an audition in three days. It should be fine, right?
لديّ اختبار أداء بعد ثلاثة أيام. من المفترض أن يكون جيدًا، أليس كذلك؟
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
I wish I could act in a scene where I have to get scared by a ghost.
أتمنى أن أتمكن من التمثيل في مشهد يجب أن أشعر فيه بالخوف من شبح.
I'm confident I could do that really well.
أنا واثق من أنني أستطيع القيام بذلك بشكل جيد حقًا.
Why don't you focus on your pronunciation?
لماذا لا تركز على نطقك؟
Your enunciation was off.
لقد كان نطقك خاطئا.
I'm probably good at acting as a damsel in distress, too.
ربما أكون جيدًا في تمثيل دور الفتاة في محنة أيضًا.
When your breath gets better, the gate of hell will close.
عندما يتحسن تنفسك، سوف تغلق أبواب الجحيم.
Then you'll be able to go back to the way you used to be.
وبعدها سوف تكون قادرًا على العودة إلى ما كنت عليه سابقًا.
That is...
إنه...
in a week?
في اسبوع؟
What?
ماذا؟
What do you mean? The time I have left here.
ماذا تقصد؟ الوقت الذي قضيته هنا.
Wow, time flies.
واو، الوقت يمر بسرعة.
Right?
يمين؟
Hey, you have nowhere to go.
مهلا، ليس لديك مكان لتذهب إليه.
Where can you rent a place with that money?
أين يمكنك استئجار مكان بهذه الأموال؟
I know the rent in Seoul better than you do.
أنا أعرف الإيجار في سيول أفضل منك.
I was going to start working full-time at the cafe in a week.
كنت سأبدأ العمل بدوام كامل في المقهى خلال أسبوع.
I'll be sleeping there, too.
سأنام هناك أيضًا.
I've already spoken to the boss.
لقد تحدثت بالفعل مع الرئيس.
Do you really want to be an actor?
هل تريد حقا أن تصبح ممثلا؟
A full-time job? When are you going to practice your acting?
وظيفة بدوام كامل؟ متى ستبدأين بالتدرب على التمثيل؟
That's why I'm trying to pass this audition.
لهذا السبب أحاول اجتياز هذا الاختبار.
Once I get the deposit, I should be able to pay the rent.
بمجرد حصولي على الوديعة، يجب أن أكون قادرًا على دفع الإيجار.
I won't need to find another job then.
لن أحتاج إلى البحث عن وظيفة أخرى بعد ذلك.
Then everything will be solved.
وبعدها سيتم حل كل شيء.
What if you fail?
ماذا لو فشلت؟
You jinx!
يا لك من نحس!
Here.
هنا.
[To: Mister] [From: Keumbok]
[إلى: السيد] [من: كيمبوك]
I was going to give this to you after the audition,
كنت سأعطيك هذا بعد الاختبار،
but I'm giving it to you first.
ولكنني أعطيك إياه أولاً.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
The rent.
الإيجار.
I prepared this as soon as I got paid.
لقد قمت بإعداد هذا بمجرد حصولي على راتبي.
Hey, we're not done charging yet, though.
مهلا، لم ننتهي من الشحن بعد، رغم ذلك.
You have to take this.
يجب عليك أن تأخذ هذا.
I'm the only normal person in this house.
أنا الشخص الطبيعي الوحيد في هذا المنزل.
Are you still not going to sleep?
هل مازلت لا تستطيع النوم؟
Are you still not coming back?
هل مازلت لا تعود؟
[No matter how busy you are, don't starve. Hunger will chase good luck away.]
مهما كنتَ مشغولاً، لا تجوع. الجوع سيُبعد الحظ السعيد.
No matter how busy you are, don't starve.
مهما كنت مشغولاً، لا تجوع.
Hunger will chase good luck away.
الجوع سوف يطرد الحظ السعيد.
The Holy Emperor's spirit-born son,
الابن المولود من روح الإمبراطور المقدس،
Bihyung-rang is his true identity.
بيهيونغ-رانغ هي هويته الحقيقية.
You multitude of ghosts who rush about,
يا أيها الجمع من الأشباح الذين يهرعون،
do not linger in this place.
لا تبقى في هذا المكان.
Gildal, you look really handsome today.
جيلدال، أنت تبدو وسيمًا حقًا اليوم.
Keumbok, you're handsome, too.
كيمبوك، أنت وسيم أيضًا.
Well...
حسنًا...
You're so charismatic.
أنت شخصية جذابة للغاية.
[Director Lee Seongtaek] ["Dear, Goblin" audition]
[المخرج لي سيونجتايك] [اختبار أداء "عزيزي، غوبلن"]
It's all over.
إنتهى الأمر.
Okay, next.
حسنا، التالي.
What? I just started.
ماذا؟ لقد بدأت للتو.
Well, you said it was over.
حسنًا، لقد قلت أن الأمر قد انتهى.
We can tell just from the first line.
يمكننا أن نقول ذلك من السطر الأول فقط.
Let the next group in.
دع المجموعة التالية تدخل.
I've been waiting for so long.
لقد كنت أنتظر لفترة طويلة.
Do you think I'll leave just 'cause you tell me to?
هل تعتقد أنني سأرحل فقط لأنك طلبت مني ذلك؟
Do you think I'm a pushover?
هل تعتقد أنني شخص سهل الإستخدام؟
What?
ماذا؟
Are you crazy?
هل انت مجنون؟
What are you doing? Get him out of here.
ماذا تفعل؟ أخرجه من هنا.
Don't get the wrong idea. Who do you think you are?
لا تسيء الفهم. من تظن نفسك؟
I won't lose you again.
لن اخسرك مرة أخرى.
If you break up with me, I'll kill you.
إذا انفصلت عني، سأقتلك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Not many people have seen my unpopular debut work.
لم يشاهد الكثير من الناس أعمالي الأولى غير المشهورة.
He's not bad.
إنه ليس سيئا.
Director Lee, no matter what...
المخرج لي، مهما كان الأمر...
How can you let a rookie do it with just a little training?
كيف يمكنك السماح للمبتدئين بالقيام بذلك بمجرد القليل من التدريب؟
Give it to him.
أعطيه له.
Also, he looks quite old-fashioned, too...
وأيضاً، فهو يبدو قديم الطراز إلى حدٍ ما، أيضاً...
This is a scene where the protagonist wants to confess his love.
هذا هو المشهد حيث يريد البطل الاعتراف بحبه.
Can you read it?
هل تستطيع قراءته؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Stress.
ضغط.
What's with your expression?
ما الأمر مع تعبيرك؟
Halmeoni.
حالموني.
Am I really just average?
هل أنا حقا مجرد متوسط؟
Objectively speaking,
من الناحية الموضوعية،
you're pretty average.
أنت متوسط ​​جدًا.
But subjectively,
ولكن من الناحية الذاتية،
from head to toe,
من الرأس إلى أخمص القدمين،
you're really average.
أنت متوسط ​​حقا.
B-But your face is the best.
ب-ولكن وجهك هو الأفضل.
Am I not classically handsome?
هل أنا لست وسيمًا بشكل كلاسيكي؟
Maybe young people nowadays don't like my looks.
ربما الشباب في أيامنا هذه لا يحبون مظهري.
Why?
لماذا؟
Did someone say you're average?
هل قال لك أحد أنك متوسط؟
How could they reject your face?
كيف يمكنهم رفض وجهك؟
There's nothing wrong with you.
لا يوجد شيء خاطئ معك.
Humans are so fickle— I can never understand them.
البشر متقلبون جدًا؟؟؟ لا أستطيع فهمهم أبدًا.
It's that human again?
هل هذا الإنسان مرة أخرى؟
You're completely under his control.
أنت تحت سيطرته بالكامل.
He said he's leaving.
قال أنه سيغادر.
Right?
يمين؟
Only Gildal can live with you.
فقط جيلدال يستطيع العيش معك.
Is it funny?
هل هذا مضحك؟
I've never seen you look like that, you brat.
لم أرى مظهرك هكذا من قبل أيها الوغد.
You look so sincere.
تبدو صادقا جدا.
Now you look like a human.
الآن تبدو وكأنك إنسان.
You call that human?
هل تسمي ذلك إنسانًا؟
You've finally met the right person.
لقد قابلت أخيرا الشخص المناسب.
Treat him well.
عامله جيدا.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Well...
حسنًا...
Just don't leave any regrets.
فقط لا تترك أي ندم.
Is there any other way? What do you think?
هل هناك طريقة أخرى؟ ما رأيك؟
He's quiet today.
إنه هادئ اليوم.
[Is this a convenient time for a call?]
[هل هذا وقت مناسب للمكالمة؟]
Is this a convenient time for a call?
هل هذا وقت مناسب للمكالمة؟
Call the clinic's front desk if you need help.
اتصل بمكتب الاستقبال في العيادة إذا كنت بحاجة إلى المساعدة.
[Is this a convenient time for a call?] [Call the clinic's front desk if you need help.]
[هل هذا وقت مناسب للمكالمة؟] [اتصل بمكتب الاستقبال في العيادة إذا كنت بحاجة إلى مساعدة.]
[Are you asleep?] [Sir, please don't contact me so early in the morning.]
[هل أنت نائم؟] [سيدي، من فضلك لا تتصل بي في هذا الوقت المبكر من الصباح.]
Are you asleep?
هل انت نائم؟
Sir, please don't contact me so early in the morning.
سيدي، من فضلك لا تتصل بي في هذا الصباح الباكر.
[The moon is so beautiful.] [Did you drink?]
[القمر جميل جدًا.] [هل شربت؟]
The moon is so beautiful.
القمر جميل جداً.
Did you drink?
هل شربت؟
[Sorry.]
[آسف.]
Sorry.
آسف.
Sir, please stop contacting me for private matters.
سيدي، من فضلك توقف عن الاتصال بي بشأن الأمور الخاصة.
[Sir, please stop contacting me for private matters.]
[سيدي، من فضلك توقف عن الاتصال بي بشأن الأمور الخاصة.]
Okay. I hope your clinic gets good business.
حسنًا، أتمنى أن تحظى عيادتك بإقبال جيد.
[Okay. I hope your clinic gets good business.] [Good luck to you too.^^]
[حسنًا. أتمنى أن تحظى عيادتك بنجاح.] [بالتوفيق لك أيضًا. ^^]
[Okay. I hope your clinic gets good business.]
[حسنًا. أتمنى أن تلقى عيادتك إقبالًا جيدًا.]
Good luck to you, too.
أتمنى لك حظا سعيدا أيضا.
[Good luck to you, too.^^]
[حظا سعيدا لك أيضا.^^]
Yes.
نعم.
Come in.
ادخل.
I don't have time to play with you.
ليس لدي وقت للعب معك.
I need to see a doctor, too.
أحتاج لرؤية الطبيب أيضًا.
What do you mean? This is a plastic surgery clinic.
ماذا تقصد؟ هذه عيادة جراحة تجميل.
I can't help but be curious,
لا أستطيع إلا أن أكون فضوليًا،
and I can't help missing you.
ولا أستطيع أن أتوقف عن افتقادك.
And right here,
وهنا بالضبط،
it feels like it's been struck by lightning—
أشعر وكأنني تعرضت لضربة برق؟؟؟
it's a tingling feeling.
إنه شعور بالوخز.
Are you really sick?
هل انت مريض حقا؟
You were there on the mountain,
كنت هناك على الجبل،
and you were at my house, too.
وكنت في بيتي أيضًا.
Hey. You've come to the wrong place.
مهلا، لقد أتيت إلى المكان الخطأ.
I've confirmed it—our relationship.
لقد تأكدت من علاقتنا.
Can you just come out here like that?
هل يمكنك أن تأتي إلى هنا هكذا؟
That kid just opened the gate of hell.
لقد فتح هذا الطفل للتو بوابة الجحيم.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I've done what it takes to repel small ghosts from him.
لقد فعلت ما يلزم لطرد الأشباح الصغيرة منه.
Yeah, well...
نعم، حسنا...
You'll take care of it.
سوف تعتني بالأمر.
At first, I hated it.
في البداية، كنت أكرهه.
I wondered why such a person existed.
لقد تساءلت لماذا يوجد مثل هذا الشخص.
Is he really an Earthling like me?
هل هو حقا إنسان أرضي مثلي؟
I didn't understand.
أنا لم أفهم.
My master...
سيدي...
So why would you pick up trash like that?
فلماذا تلتقط القمامة بهذه الطريقة؟
Why are you doing things no one asked you to?
لماذا تفعل أشياء لم يطلبها منك أحد؟
Who are you to care about me?
من أنت لتهتم بي؟
You should keep this for yourself.
ينبغي عليك الاحتفاظ بهذا لنفسك.
You're really...
أنت حقا...
sensitive, irritable,
حساس، سريع الانفعال،
and picky.
وانتقائي.
I keep thinking of you.
أنا أستمر في التفكير بك.
What are you looking at?
ماذا تنظر اليه؟
Thank you for today.
شكرا لك على اليوم.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
You little...
أنت صغير...
Move!
يتحرك!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
It's safe around here at night.
إنه مكان آمن هنا في الليل.
Just letting you know.
فقط أريد أن أعلمك.
Do you...
هل أنت...
like...
يحب...
I like you, from the bottom of my heart.
أنا أحبك من أعماق قلبي.
You must really like them.
لا بد وأنك تحبهم حقًا.
What? I was just reading from the script.
ماذا؟ كنت أقرأ من النص فقط.
That wasn't it.
لم يكن هذا هو الأمر.
You were thinking about someone, weren't you?
لقد كنت تفكر في شخص ما، أليس كذلك؟
Thank you for your performance, Ha Keumbok.
شكرا لك على أدائك، ها كومبوك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I miss him? What the hell.
أفتقده؟ ماذا بحق الجحيم؟
Found it.
وجدته.
Love is like eating.
الحب مثل الأكل.
You need to give what the other person likes.
يجب عليك أن تعطي للشخص الآخر ما يحبه.
What if you can't?
ماذا لو لم تتمكن من ذلك؟
Then just give a little
ثم أعط القليل فقط
and take it back.
وخذها مرة أخرى.
Give a little,
أعطي القليل
and take it back. Just like this.
واسترجعها. هكذا تمامًا.
It's like playing hard to get.
إنه مثل اللعب على أنه من الصعب الحصول عليه.
I'm a master.
أنا سيد.
I'm just waiting for my love to show up. Where are they?
أنا فقط أنتظر ظهور حبيبي. أين هم؟
-Hey. -Yes?
-مرحبا. -نعم؟
-Actors wait here— -No.
-الممثلين ينتظرون هنا؟؟؟ -لا.
He's about this tall and has a small face.
إنه طويل بهذا القدر وله وجه صغير.
Anyway, I'm looking for a guy called Ha Keumbok.
على أية حال، أنا أبحث عن رجل يدعى ها كومبوك.
I'm not sure.
أنا لست متأكدا.
Ha Keumbok!
في كومبوك!
You're late.
لقد تأخرت.
You...
أنت...
It's fun.
إنه ممتع.
If you misuse your power now,
إذا أسأت استخدام قوتك الآن،
you might never come back alive.
ربما لن تعود حيًا أبدًا.
Are you going to keep making me conscious of you?
هل ستستمر في جعلني واعيًا بك؟
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Can I hold onto you?
هل يمكنني التمسك بك؟
It's night, after all.
إنه الليل، بعد كل شيء.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
But...
لكن...
you came to save me.
لقد أتيت لإنقاذي.
Give me your hand.
أعطني يدك.
Again?
مرة أخرى؟
Do you want to go to the gate of hell then?
هل تريد أن تذهب إلى بوابة الجحيم إذن؟
Give me your hand.
أعطني يدك.
You're a genius.
أنت عبقري.